KEVIN G. SALINAS

CONTACT

Kevin G. Salinas 5042 64th Street #2F Woodside, NY 11377

Email: KevinGSP@gmail.com Phone: + (646) 812-4992

Website: www.kevingsalinas.me LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/kevingsp

EDUCATION

B.S. IN INFORMATICS

University at Albany, DEC 2016 Major: UX Design & Social Media Analytics GPA: 3.42

Organizations

ACM, Base^64, ASIS&T, GreenScene, Rockefeller, Advistment Services

Projects

NY State Concourse Gallery Redesign Albany Law Map API NY.GOV Redesign

SKILLS

UX/UI Design HTML/CSS

Photoshop InDesign

Prototyping Wireframes

Agile Scrum SQL

Bootstrap Javascript

Project Management

Content Management

PROFILE

An experienced Apple technician with a passion for design. I've always strived to provide the best customer experience possible by being empathetic and understanding, while creating a comfortable environment of trust. I want to bring my love for creation and my customer service experience into one, where I can create products that are user-friendly and effective.

EXPERIENCE

ENJOY | FROM JUN 2018 - PRESENT Field & Fulfillment Expert

Enjoy is a startup company that's changing the way products are delivered at home. We partner with different brands to provide a full setup experience, answers questions, and carry a mobile inventory with extra products so we can bring the store to the customer. I am certified in AT&T POS, Sonos Hardware & Software, Magic Leap Virtual Reality, and Google Hardware & Software. We use G-Suite and Slack to communicate, and our own in-house apps to manage inventory and deliveries. Our in-house app allows us to conduct routine audits of inventory levels to maintain accuracy, pick, pack and fulfill orders, and load inventory to our vehicles.

APPLE, INC. | FROM OCT 2015 - MAY 2018 Genius

Also known as a Senior Technician, being a Genius at Apple means you become a resource on the floor, find ways to improve the customer experience, and properly train and develop the team—with mentorship roles set up, quarterly meetings, and metric reviews. While delivering an exceptional customer experience, I also diagnosed and troubleshot issues on the spot, provided options, explained potential solutions, all in a fast-paced, crowded environment. Juggling multiple customers was a major part of my job and was essential to my success, so much that it became second nature. I provided feedback, set up development goals for my team, prioritized customer's needs as needed, was always able to deescalate situations, and make quick decisions in the moment.

Technical Expert

A master of iOS and MacOS for both hardware and software troubleshooting. I went through extensive training and shadowing where I was able to learn the hands-on repair aspect of iOS and MacOS devices. I did hands on repairs on all models of iPhones and Macs within a timely fashion. Kept track of repairs that came in, prioritized by appointment time and necessity, assessed our Genius Room environment and saw if changes needed to be made to have a fast and productive pace.

ROCKEFELLER COLLEGE | FROM SEPT 2016 - SEPT 2017 Web Master & Content Manager

Managed and updated website for Rockefeller College and individual departments. Used Dreamweaver and FTP software to update the websites in real time. Created templates with HTML/CSS & JavaScript to align with the University's theme. Worked on multiple projects concurrently and supported various directors with different goals and perspectives on how to generate more user interaction.

UNIVERSITY AT ALBANY | FROM MAY 2016 - JAN 2017 Web Developer

Revamped and optimized department website for the Advisement Center. Introduced new features that made information easier to access and maneuver. Created wireframes and brought them to life, coding them from scratch. Used content management software OpenText/RedDot, to update multiple pages at once and create content specific webpages.